var questions = [
   {
   
    question: "Question of 1K on your screen is as follows:\n1.How many infinity stones are there mentioned in AVENGERS?\nA.3\nB.5\nC.6\nD.7\nYour answer: ",
    amount: "\nCongratulations!,Your account balance has now: 1000 rupees which you will surely collect from here!",
   answer: ["C","C-6"]
  },
   {
     question: "Question of 2k on your screen now!:\n2.Which IPL team has won maximum number of titles till date ?\nA.CSK\nB.RR\nC.PBKS\nD.MI\nYour answer: ",
     amount: "\nCongratulations!,Your account balance has now: 2000 rupees which you will surely collect from here!", 
     answer: ["D","D-RCB"]
    
   },
   { 
    question: "Question of 3k on your screen!:\n3.Who is the leader of Tapusena of famous TMKOC T.V serial?\nA.Sonu\nB.Pinku\nC.Tipendra\nD.Gogi\nYour answer: ",
    amount: "\nCongratulations!,Your account balance has now: 3000 rupees which you will surely collect from  here!",
     answer: ["C","C-Tipendra"]
   },

   {
     question: "Question of 5K on your screen!:\n4.In the game of ludo the discs or tockens are of how many colors? \nA.1\nB.2\nC.3\nD.4\nYour answer: ",
    amount: "\nCongratulations!,Your account balance has now: 5000 rupees which you will surely collect from here!",
     answer: ["D","D-4"]
   },

   {
      question: "Question of 10K on your screen!\n5.What is the name of Harry potter's owl in movie-Harry potter\nA.Hedwig\nB.Ozwald\nC.Elvis\nD.Bert\nYour answer: ",
     amount: "\nCongratulations!,Your account balance has now: 50000 rupees which you will surely collect from here!",
     answer: ["A","A-Hedwig"]
   },
  {
    question: "Question of 50K on your screen!\n6.Which of the following term/terms can only be used for woman ?\nA.Dirgayu\nB.Suhagan\nC.Chiranjivi\nD.Both B and C \nYour answer: ",
    amount: "\nCongratulations!,Your account balance has now: 50k rupees which you will surely collect from here!",
   answer: ["B" , "B-Suhagan"]
   },

   {
    question: "Good going Sir,Question of 1 Lac now on your screen!\n7.The wife of which of these famous sports persons was once captain of Indian volleyball team?\nA.K.D. Jadhav\nB.Dhyan Chand\nC.Prakash Padukone\nD.Milkha Singh\nYour answer: ",
    amount: "\nCongratulations!,Your account balance has now: 1 lac rupees which you will surely collect from here!",
     answer: ["D","D-Milkha Singh"] 
   },
  

 {
   question: "Question of 5 Lac now on your screen!\n8.Who wrote the introduction to the English translation of Rabindranath Tagore’s Gitanjali?\nA.P.B. Shelley\nB.Alfred Tennyson\nC.W.B. Yeats\nD.T.S. Elliot\nYour answer: ",
   amount: "\nCongratulations!,Your account balance has now: 5 Lac rupees which you will surely collect from here!",
     answer: ["C", "C-W.B Yeats"]
 },

 {
   question: "Question of 10 Lac is now on your screen!\n9. Where was the BRICS summit held in 2014?\nA.Brazil\nB.India\nC.Russia\nD.Finland\nYour answer: ",
   amount: "\nCongratulations!,Your account balance has now: 10 Lac rupees which you will surely collect from here!",
    answer: ["A", "A-Brazil"]

 },

 {
   question: "Question of 25 Lac is now on your screen!\n10.Which of these are names of national parks located in Madhya Pradesh?\nA.Krishna and Kanhaiya\nB. Kanha and Madhav\nC.Ghanshyam and Murari\nD.Girdhar and Gopal\nYour answer: ",
   amount: "\nCongratulations!,Your account balance has now: 25 Lac rupees which you will surely collect from here!",
     answer: ["B", "B-Kanha and Madhav"]
},

{
  question: "Question of 50 Lac is now on your screen!\n11.India’s official entry to Oscars 2021, ” Jallikattu” is, a film in which language?\nA.Hindi\nB.Kannada\nC.Malyalam\nD.Punjabi\nYour answer: ",
  amount: "\nCongratulations!,Your account balance has now: 50 Lac rupees which you will surely collect from here!",
  answer: ["C","C-Malyalam"]

},
{
question: "You are playing it amazing!onto the Question of 1 CRORE! now on your screen!\n12.Who is 'YOU KNOW WHO in the famous Harry potter series?\nA.Harry potter\nB.Voldemort\nC.Severus Snape\nD.Antonin dolohov\nYour answer: ",
amount: "\nCongratulations!,Your account balance has now: 1 CRORE rupees which you will surely collect from here!",
answer: ["B","B-Voldemort"]
},

{
question: "Question of 5 CRORE is now on your screen!\n13.Which player holds the record for the fastest fifty in IPL?\nA.Yuvraj Singh\nB.Yusuf Pathan\nC.K.L.Rahul\nD.Chris Gayle\nYour answer: ",
amount: "\nCongratulations!,Your account balance has now: 5 CRORE rupees which you will surely collect from here!",
answer: ["C","C-K.L.Rahul"]

},
{
  question: "Question of  10 CRORE is now on your screen!\n14.Which season/(s) of IPL had the most number of hat-tricks?\nA.2009\nB.2008 and 2017\nC.2010 and 2016\nD.2019\nYour answer: ",
  amount: "\nCongratulations!,Your account balance has now: 10 CRORE rupees which you will surely collect from here!",
  answer: ["B","B-2008 and 2017"]

}



]



module.exports = questions